redline-software.com 2008-11-12

# Red Line Software :: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.**

Red Line Software respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting your privacy throughout your use of our website.

When you place an order online, we redirect you to the third-party website, provided by ShareIt! ShareIt! has its own privacy policy; please read it before placing an order.

We do not gather any credit card information from your product registration (we have no such technical capability) and we do not keep any information of the sort.

For your own privacy, please do not send us any credit card information via open channels (e.g. to our support e-mail). Use this information only when placing your order via ShareIt!

We also do not collect any personal information from you.

If you subscribe to our subscription services, you will be required to provide your name and an e-mail address. This information will not be shared with any third party, nor will it be used for unsolicited e-mail communication.

We use cookies on our website only to collect general usage information, such as aggregated website traffic statistics. A cookie is a small file that a website saves to your hard drive when you visit the site. A cookie is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It is a kind of ID and cannot deliver viruses. Cookies can not read information from your hard drive, nor information from other cookies. Cookies are not used to collect your personal information. You can disable cookies in the Internet Options of your browser.

Cookies help us determine what information is most valuable to you so we can improve our services and the website.

This site contains references to third-party web pages. We do not bear any responsibility for their privacy practices. To make sure your private information is secure you should read the respective privacy statements of these third parties.

We reserve the right to update this privacy statement from time to time. If we change our privacy statement, a clear notice will be published on our website.
